STEPHEN OKYERE

Frontend Developer

★ stephenokyere621@gmail.com
★ stephenokyere233

**** 0204094879

3217 Cantoment-Accra

dev_steve

portfolio

PROFILE

Skilled frontend developer with expertise in React, Next.is, and Tailwind. I craft stunning, intuitive websites and mobile apps that deliver exceptional user experiences. Turning your vision into reality on the web, one pixel at a time.

SKILLS

Techical Skills (Next]S, React]S, Javascript, Redux, HTML, CSS, GIT, Tailwind CSS, React Native, SaSS, Firebase).

Industry Knowledge (UX/UI, Testing, Debugging, Usability Research, REST APIs & integrations)

PROIECTS

Palmplayy, Music Streaming web app *⊘* I recently built this music streaming app with Next|S, Tailwind CSS, Shazam API, Redux and Context API. The app takes all the music data from the shazam api and displays it with good UI, where you're able to find lyrics song details and artist details

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

08/2022 - present | Lagos, Nigeria

- Knowledgeable about the current syntax (ES6 minimum), fluent in JavaScript, and well-versed in React.is. Having experience using APIs and Frontend development tools like HTML, CSS, Redux, and Tailwind CSS and Next.js.
- Worked in an atmosphere that was both adaptable and collaborative for software development, constantly learning both front-end and back-end procedures while focusing on the front-end.
- Contributed closely with visual designers to deliver wireframes from conception to implementation, and Back-end developers to ensure tested and production-ready UI code.

Frontend Developer

07/2022 - present

- I made it a point to find open source projects and made good contibutions to then
- Built UI for some projects like LinkFree, WhisChat, TweetSage and other which all got reviewed and merged.

EDUCATION

IPMC ₽

03/2022 - present | Accra, Ghana